[wind gusting]
[disguised robotic voice]
I got a message
to meet someone here.
Were you followed?
[chuckles] If you thought
I could be followed,
you wouldn't have sent
a message to me
in the first place.
Huh. True.
So, what do you need me for?
Revenge.
I want you
to bring someone to me.
Interesting,
but let's be clear.
Delivering people
is a lot more expensive
than delivering things.
You got that kind of cash?
Don't let my appearance
fool you.
I am not without resources.
Who's the target?
I'll pay you five times
your regular fee.
Hmm.
This target must be important.
Long ago, he and my sister
betrayed my family,
but that is not your business.
Do we have a deal?
[wind gusting]
[♪♪♪]
Sir, Arrakore,
if you would please, sir,
could you heal my flower?
I've tried everything!
Is that a question or a wish?
A wish! Right.
[clearing throat]
I wish my flower was blooming!
Your wish is yours to keep.
[stone rumbling]
[gasping in delight]
You're back to looking
like your usual
beautiful self, Veronica.
Your wish is yours to keep!
[stone rumbling]
I wish to become
a real Spinjitzu Ninja,
like, for permanent.
[sighing]
Uh-uh.
[♪♪♪]
Seriously?
What gives?
I am never obligated
to grant a wish.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, but...
Pretty please?
Mm... no.
I can refuse for any reason.
Sometimes it's beyond
the limits of my power,
and sometimes I just don't think
it's a good idea.
Which one is it this time?
Both.
Definitely both.
[thunderclaps booming]
Huh?
What the crackle?
This cannot be good.
♪ Lost in the unknown ♪
♪ Together we will rise ♪
♪ We fight ♪
♪ Be a ninja
for what's right ♪
[thunderclaps]
[♪♪♪]
[panting in fear]
I wish to be safe in bed
right now!
[panting]
Still no?
Come on! Can't you hear me?
And who might you be?
I am Rox.
Of the Forbidden Five.
Never heard of you.
Do not worry.
Soon the entire world will cower
at the sound of my name,
but that's not why I'm here.
You will repair this blade.
[scoffing] You wish.
I know exactly
what this blade is,
and what evil
it can be used for.
Does anyone have any clue
what this thing can be used for?
[wind gusting]
[♪♪♪]
Found anything about
Prismatic blades in there yet?
No.
There should be an index
or something,
a table of contents.
-[slamming]
-[groaning in frustration]
We should be out there
looking for the Forbidden Five!
Who knows what kind of damage
they're doing now?
Look for them where?
I don't know,
but I do know
that they aren't hiding
in this book!
Whatever the Forbidden Five
wanted with the sword
is of grave importance--
"Grave" is probably right.
So we need to learn
more about it.
"You're so right, Nya!
As per usual."
I would never say that.
Here!
Prismatic Steel!
Everything's
in alphabetical order.
[sputtering and stammering]
Well, why didn't Roby
tell me that?
According to this,
if you look through
a Prismatic Blade,
it can reveal
hidden souls around us.
The blade was not forged
in fire,
but the resonance
of soul energy.
Hidden souls?
[shuddering] Creeptastic.
Get this--
eons ago, there was this dragon
named ThunderFang,
who was desperate to become
a Source Dragon.
When all his attempts failed,
he became enraged,
bitter...
and tried to destroy
everything in his path.
The only thing
that defeated him was--
A giant comet! Quicksand!
Heartburn...
Stop talking.
The only thing
that defeated ThunderFang
was the Arc Dragon of Focus.
ThunderFang,
who they called
a Shatter Dragon of Chaos,
was then imprisoned,
with chains
that could only be cut
by five Prismatic blades.
[gasping]
This must be
what the Forbidden Five
wanted that blade for!
To free
an ancient Dragon of Chaos
that tried to destroy the world?
Don't like the sound of that.
We gotta warn the other Ninja.
[wind gusting]
[thunder rumbling]
[grunting and struggling]
You will repair this.
I choose to grant wishes
only to those
whose need is pure.
If you won't help me
by choice...
[gasping]
[shuddering]
Ah... you do know what this is.
Once I trap you inside here,
you will be my servant,
and have no choice
but to grant my wishes.
Never.
[roaring]
Get him!
I'm still so weak...
[panting]
[snarling]
[breathing hard]
You're lucky the Ninja
aren't here.
They would defeat you with ease.
You're no match for my friends!
I think you mean the Ninja
are no match for us!
Get him!
Really?
The Ninja have only
saved the world...
many times!
You're nothing
compared to them.
How dare you!
I wish the Ninja were here.
Then you would see how easily
I would crush them!
Your wish is yours to keep.
[gasping]
That was weird, right?
But how do we even
find the others?
Maybe we can--
Maybe we can what, Nya?
Don't leave me hanging--
Nya? Nya?
[gasping] Oof.
[Riyu whining]
Nya?
What's going on here?
No clue. One minute I was--
[Arrakore] Ninja!
[snarling]
A little help here, please!
-Arrakore!
Ninja... go!
Whoa...! [sputtering]
[groaning]
Sloppy.
Embrace your anger.
Find your strength!
I'm trying.
You're failing.
You're letting your emotions
get the best of you.
I just found out
my parents are dead.
And who is responsible
for their deaths?
Master Wu.
[roaring angrily]
There.
Your anger gives you strength.
Power.
Are you certain you can
bring my parents back?
Yes, but it will not be easy.
The Merge can only be undone
with power
from all seven Source Dragons.
And how do we get that?
Each of the Source Dragons
must heed the call
of their own Icons,
which can only be used once.
That is how I summoned
the Source Dragon of Energy,
which Imperium helped me contain
under their city,
never knowing my ultimate goals.
But Imperium was not ready
to contain two dragons...
hence I've been carrying
the Icon of
the Source Dragon of Strength
with me all this time,
but we need Icons
for the other six,
and ways to contain them.
[roaring]
I had planned to create
new Icons
with the Elemental Powers
I gathered at the Tournament,
until the Forbidden Five
betrayed me.
Now we must find other ways
to obtain the Icons we need.
If that will bring
my parents back,
I'll help you.
Whatever it takes.
[roaring
and shouting battle cries]
[Nya] Happy to help, but--
[grunting with effort]
What's the deal here?
They wish for me to reassemble
a shattered Prismatic blade!
[Nya] What?
I hope you refused!
No, we're fighting
because I agreed to do
everything they wanted.
H'yah!
[grunting with impact]
[Sora] A Prisma-what-now blade?
[Nya] Prismatic Steel
is a metal
that looks like crystal.
It's made of soul energy.
Deeply weird.
[Sora] No way!
We found one of those blades
when we were looking for Arin!
The Forbidden Five
tried to get ours!
You gather
five of those blades,
and you can unlock
this big, bad news,
world-killing
Shatter Dragon of Chaos
named ThunderFang!
Did I somehow not know
you were a Prismatic Steel
super-fan?
[grunting]
I'm not.
I just learned all that,
like, three minutes ago!
[gasping]
[grunting]
Looks like Rox is hoping
wish magic can fix her blade.
Wish magic...
[roaring]
[grunting with effort] Hup!
H'yah!
Despite the circumstances,
I gotta say,
I love what you've done
with the place.
I've been working very hard
to try to restore Djinjago
wish by wish.
Well, maybe I can
help with that.
I wish Rox and the Dragonians
would disappear!
[Nya] Brilliant!
[Arrakore] Your wish is...
too big for me to grant.
What? But-but-but
I did the thing.
I said "I wish."
I'm so sorry.
Wish magic comes from
Djinjago itself.
Though our realm
is bigger than it once was,
it's nowhere near
its former glory.
Bringing you here
took almost
all the strength I had.
I can only do small wishes,
maybe.
I wish Rox's feet
were stuck to the ground!
-[Sora] Ha!
-[Rox growling]
I wish you could see your face!
It's just an expression,
never mind!
Nya! Riyu!
Wishes work,
just keep 'em small,
and weird,
mostly 'cause that's fun for me.
[Nya] I wish this guy
would be jolted by lightning!
[wheezing]
[laughing] Nice!
[stone rumbling]
[Nya] I wish he was
as light as a feather!
[roaring]
[excited grunting language]
One rubber ball coming up!
[bouncing]
Nice one, Riyu!
How you holding up?
I'm a Djinn.
This is my true purpose!
Keep wishing!
[Nya] I wish this Dragonian
had bones made of jelly!
[Sora] I wish
this Dragonian's helmet
was on backwards!
[grunting] H'yah!
[stone rumbling]
[gasping wearily]
[groaning]
[Nya] We gotta scale back
the wishing
and do more Ninjaing!
[grunting]
[roaring battle cries]
[grunting with effort]
There's no technology
I can use
to channel
my Elemental Powers here!
[Riyu grunting]
But I do have feet.
[grunting]
[shouting battle cry]
[growling]
[chanting] Niver-maste
fo le ana-ton go so-lox
pezotan menoo-gala poxel...
-No!
...guthero-vix da sempaste to!
[Arrakore shouting] No!
[Sora gasping]
[grunting with impact]
Let me out!
I will never grant your wishes,
no matter what you may do to me!
[Rox] You are my prisoner.
My servant.
You must grant my wishes now.
I wish
you would repair my blade!
[gasping and struggling]
Your wish is yours to keep.
[Sora] You're not getting
out of here with Arrakore!
Or that Prismatic blade!
We know you plan
to release ThunderFang!
And you three
are going to stop me?
Ha!
This isn't our first fight.
[grunting]
It's the first fight
where I have the power
of a Djinn on my side.
I wish you would freeze!
[Nya] Really?
Is that the only trick--
[frozen voice mumbling]
Ha ha!
I should just accept my victory
and leave,
or wish now for your doom,
but this is too good.
I wish for the Ninja to admit
that the Forbidden Five
are their true superiors
in every way.
[together, Riyu grunting]
The Forbidden Five
are our true superiors
in every way.
[Rox cackling]
Too much fun.
I wish for the Ninja
to unfreeze,
so that they may bow down
before me.
[Sora gasping]
This is humiliating.
[stone rumbling]
[Nya] I don't love it,
but at least even these wishes
help restore Arrakore's realm.
[stone rumbling]
[Sora] A realm
Arrakore's never going
to be able to return to.
[mechanism whirring]
I don't think that's
just a container.
It's a timepiece!
So?
You have an appointment
you need to keep or something?
[Sora] No, Nya, it's tech!
[Nya] Oh...
this is gonna be good.
Why didn't I think
of imprisoning you sooner,
Arrakore?
This is pure bliss.
Now...
I wish for the Ninja
to get up...
[powering up]
...and walk off
the edge of the--
[rattling, power surging]
[Rox] What?
Impossible!
I'm free!
[Rox stammering] Uh...
I wish you would--
You have no power over me, Rox!
[Rox] Get him!
Get out of here, Arrakore!
[grunting with effort]
Don't make me wish it.
[♪♪♪]
[grunting] H'ah!
[grunting with effort]
[roaring]
[wind whistling]
[grunting with effort] Ha!
Young ninja team for the win!
[Riyu screeching in triumph]
[♪♪♪]
We got what we came for!
Three of the blades are ours!
Let us go!
[grunting with effort]
H'ah!
They're gone?
Oh, thank goodness.
[groaning]
Boy, you have grown,
little dragon.
[Riyu screeching fondly]
Are you okay?
[groaning] I will be.
You saved me.
Just like I knew you would.
Well, that battle
definitely helped you
grow Djinjago a bit more.
[stones rumbling]
I would have preferred
if we'd grown the realm
by granting wishes for kittens
or something.
Ooh, we still could.
No.
[chuckling]
[coughing weakly]
[groaning]
I still have enough energy
to grant one more wish today.
Please.
Anything you want, you may have.
[whispering] Kittens...
let's wish for kittens, come on!
Sora, really?
I'm kidding!
Sort of.
Okay, what I'd really
wish to know
is where
our missing friends are.
Ah, I wish I could tell you,
but that is beyond
my spent powers.
I'm sorry.
You have
nothing to be sorry for.
You've done
incredible things for us
and your realm,
and one day,
you will restore Djinjago
to what it once was.
No.
You'll make it even better.
But is there a chance
you could send us back
to where you got us?
Hmm, now, that... I can do.
Can I say the thing?
Do the honors.
I wish we would all go back
to join our friends.
Your wish is yours to keep.
[gasping]
[stone rumbling]
[grunting]
Sora!
Where have you been--
[grunting]
Ow.
Ah! [grunting]
What the heck, Nya?
You've been hiding
this whole time
just to prank attack me?
Good job.
I wish I'd thought of that.
--and then Arrakore
sent us back
to where we came from.
So you had another run-in
with Rox?
Yeah, and our problem
with the Forbidden Five
just got worse.
Nya knows
why the Forbidden Five
are collecting
the Prismatic blades.
They are definitely
going to unlock ThunderFang,
the Shatter Dragon of Chaos.
And they have
three of the five blades
to do it now.
We have one.
So, where is the fifth blade?
No idea.
Sorry, Nya,
but finding Jay
will have to wait.
We need to hunt down
that fifth blade
before the Forbidden Five does.
[wind gusting]
[♪♪♪]
Whew!
Where are we going now?
You tell me.
Huh?
How did you and the Ninja learn
of the Source Dragon energy
in the Dragon Cores?
There was this place
in the World Forest.
The Temple of the Dragon Cores.
Can you show me
how to get there?
Yes.
[♪♪♪]